{"tokens": ["The", "Barcelona", "managerial", "situation", "has", "been", "the", "subject", "of", "speculation", "ever", "since", "Xavi", "Hernandez", "announced", "that", "he", "would", "be", "stepping", "down", "as", "head", "coach", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "season", "Club", "bosses", "wonâ", "t", "rush", "into", "making", "a", "decision", "although", "there", "has", "been", "plenty", "of", "noise", "over", "the", "last", "two", "weeks", "Barca", "Atletic", "coach", "Rafael", "Marquez", "and", "Bolognaâ", "s", "Thiago", "Motta", "have", "both", "been", "linked", "with", "the", "position", "although", "as", "Fabrizio", "Romano", "has", "told", "Caught", "Offside", "in", "his", "exclusive", "column", "neither", "are", "in", "line", "to", "be", "a", "serious", "candidate", "The", "same", "can", "be", "said", "for", "Antonio", "Conte", "who", "reportedly", "offered", "himself", "to", "Barcelona", "in", "recent", "days", "â", "Iâ", "m", "told", "itâ", "s", "not", "true", "that", "Antonio", "Conte", "has", "been", "offered", "to", "the", "club", "as", "a", "candidate", "to", "be", "their", "next", "manager", "At", "the", "moment", "there", "is", "nothing", "ongoing", "between", "Conte", "and", "Barca", "itâ", "s", "all", "quiet", "The", "same", "is", "true", "with", "Thiago", "Motta", "â", "he", "is", "not", "in", "the", "frame", "for", "the", "job", "at", "the", "moment", "heâ", "s", "going", "to", "stay", "in", "Italy", "and", "work", "in", "Italy", "next", "season", "Itâ", "s", "also", "completely", "quiet", "with", "Rafael", "Marquez", "â", "Romano", "also", "addressed", "the", "ongoing", "speculation", "surrounding", "Hansi", "Flick", "who", "has", "emerged", "as", "a", "leading", "contender", "for", "the", "Barcelona", "job", "â", "With", "Hansi", "Flick", "Iâ", "m", "told", "he", "would", "be", "super", "happy", "to", "come", "to", "Barca", "heâ", "s", "super", "open", "to", "this", "possibility", "But", "itâ", "s", "on", "Barca", "â", "Laporta", "and", "Deco", "have", "to", "decide", "who", "is", "the", "manager", "they", "want", "and", "at", "the", "moment", "they", "have", "not", "made", "a", "decision", "it", "will", "still", "be", "some", "time", "before", "we", "know", "the", "new", "Barca", "coach", "â", "There", "are", "sure", "to", "be", "plenty", "of", "twists", "and", "turns", "on", "the", "Barcelona", "managerial", "situation", "over", "the", "coming", "months", "One", "thing", "for", "certain", "is", "that", "Xavi", "is", "not", "considering", "staying", "on", "in", "the", "role", "despite", "an", "upturn", "in", "form", "over", "the", "last", "couple", "of", "weeks"], "iob_tags": ["O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Akram", "Afif", "is", "the", "first", "ever", "player", "to", "score", "a", "hat", "trick", "in", "the", "Asian", "Cup", "final", "ð", "He", "scored", "three", "penalties", "against", "Jordan", "to", "help", "Qatar", "win", "back", "to", "back", "Asian", "Cups", "and", "take", "his", "tally", "to", "eight", "for", "the", "tournament", "winning", "himself", "the", "Golden", "Boot", "In", "doing", "so", "he", "also", "became", "just", "the", "third", "player", "to", "score", "8", "goals", "in", "a", "single", "edition", "of", "the", "tournament", "after", "Ali", "Daei", "1996", "and", "teammate", "Almoez", "Ali", "2019"], "iob_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Manchester", "United", "legend", "Gary", "Neville", "has", "called", "his", "former", "club", "naÃ", "ve", "after", "years", "of", "operating", "without", "a", "sporting", "director", "Mail", "Sport", "exclusively", "revealed", "on", "Wednesday", "that", "the", "Red", "Devils", "are", "on", "the", "cusp", "of", "reaching", "an", "agreement", "with", "Newcastle", "over", "sporting", "director", "Dan", "Ashworth", "who", "is", "keen", "on", "swapping", "St", "James", "Park", "for", "Old", "Trafford", "The", "52", "year", "old", "is", "seen", "as", "the", "best", "in", "the", "business", "by", "incoming", "Man", "United", "co", "owner", "Sir", "Jim", "Ratcliffe", "and", "his", "INEOS", "team", "and", "the", "focus", "of", "his", "remit", "would", "be", "recruitment", "Ashworth", "has", "not", "had", "as", "much", "control", "as", "he", "expected", "at", "Newcastle", "the", "club", "he", "joined", "in", "the", "summer", "of", "2022", "There", "has", "been", "no", "fallout", "but", "it", "is", "thought", "the", "lure", "of", "the", "project", "at", "Man", "United", "and", "his", "relationship", "with", "INEOS", "director", "of", "sport", "Sir", "Dave", "Brailsford", "has", "persuaded", "him", "the", "time", "is", "right", "to", "move", "on", "Discussing", "Ashworth", "s", "imminent", "move", "to", "Old", "Trafford", "on", "the", "Stick", "to", "Football", "podcast", "by", "Sky", "Bet", "Neville", "urged", "that", "Manchester", "United", "have", "been", "naÃ", "ve", "and", "lost", "out", "on", "millions", "during", "negotiations", "without", "a", "sporting", "director", "Agents", "have", "a", "bad", "reputation", "in", "football", "but", "ultimately", "they", "won", "t", "do", "someone", "over", "that", "they", "work", "well", "with", "because", "they", "won", "t", "get", "the", "next", "gig", "If", "an", "agent", "screwed", "over", "Liverpool", "that", "agent", "wouldn", "t", "work", "with", "Liverpool", "again", "and", "it", "would", "spread", "quite", "quickly", "Neville", "said", "Manchester", "United", "haven", "t", "had", "a", "sporting", "director", "for", "the", "last", "10", "years", "so", "they", "ve", "been", "so", "naÃ", "ve", "at", "that", "level", "I", "imagine", "when", "they", "ve", "been", "dealing", "with", "agents", "if", "United", "called", "you", "you", "knew", "you", "were", "going", "to", "get", "another", "Â", "20", "30million", "because", "they", "were", "naÃ", "ve", "and", "didn", "t", "have", "a", "relationship", "with", "agents", "Recruitment", "is", "Ratcliffe", "s", "number", "one", "priority", "at", "Manchester", "United", "with", "the", "rebuild", "of", "Old", "Trafford", "secondary", "INEOS", "are", "determined", "to", "find", "a", "better", "balance", "to", "recruitment", "than", "what", "has", "been", "achieved", "over", "the", "past", "10", "years", "and", "have", "identified", "Ashworth", "as", "the", "ideal", "lead", "to", "a", "new", "look", "team", "After", "impressing", "at", "West", "Bromwich", "Albion", "Ashworth", "became", "the", "FA", "s", "Director", "of", "Elite", "Development", "in", "2012", "and", "pioneered", "England", "DNA", "a", "player", "development", "plan", "for", "both", "the", "men", "s", "and", "women", "s", "teams", "Despite", "attracting", "interest", "from", "United", "Ashworth", "moved", "to", "Brighton", "as", "technical", "director", "in", "2019", "before", "taking", "on", "his", "new", "role", "at", "St", "James", "Park", "in", "February", "2022", "Neville", "continued", "Dan", "Ashworth", "did", "a", "good", "job", "at", "West", "Brom", "but", "I", "was", "there", "with", "England", "when", "he", "was", "appointed", "and", "it", "was", "a", "big", "change", "when", "he", "came", "in", "It", "was", "quite", "a", "jolt", "at", "the", "time", "for", "Roy", "Hodgson", "to", "have", "a", "technical", "director", "like", "Dan", "Ashworth", "who", "then", "brought", "in", "Dave", "Reddin", "who", "was", "a", "performance", "director", "This", "was", "then", "they", "started", "talking", "about", "different", "types", "of", "coaches", "e", "g", "attacking", "and", "defending", "coaches", "and", "they", "were", "talking", "about", "attacking", "set", "piece", "coaches", "breaking", "the", "game", "down", "to", "intimate", "detail", "which", "was", "something", "Roy", "wasn", "t", "used", "to", "I", "remember", "Dan", "having", "a", "conversation", "with", "Roy", "but", "they", "were", "building", "all", "these", "foundations", "where", "he", "started", "with", "the", "U21s", "the", "U18s", "and", "with", "the", "women", "s", "team", "You", "think", "of", "the", "success", "of", "all", "those", "teams", "in", "recent", "years", "but", "that", "has", "been", "in", "the", "making", "for", "eight", "years", "and", "it", "all", "started", "when", "Dan", "came", "in", "Iâ", "m", "not", "saying", "heâ", "s", "responsible", "for", "what", "happened", "but", "he", "had", "a", "big", "influence", "with", "FA", "They", "were", "a", "terrible", "organisation", "from", "a", "professionalism", "point", "of", "view", "and", "I", "felt", "what", "he", "did", "he", "put", "processes", "in", "place", "where", "theyâ", "re", "now", "structured", "and", "organised"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["In", "another", "thrilling", "weekend", "of", "Premier", "League", "action", "the", "agony", "and", "ecstasy", "of", "the", "world", "s", "premier", "football", "competition", "was", "on", "full", "display", "Excitement", "has", "thus", "far", "being", "the", "name", "of", "the", "game", "and", "the", "2023", "24", "season", "is", "on", "course", "to", "set", "a", "new", "record", "for", "total", "goals", "in", "Premier", "League", "history", "Manchester", "City", "Arsenal", "and", "Liverpool", "all", "picked", "up", "wins", "to", "strengthen", "their", "title", "ambitions", "with", "all", "three", "showing", "no", "signs", "of", "slowing", "down", "their", "charge", "towards", "the", "top", "spot", "as", "we", "approach", "the", "final", "third", "of", "the", "campaign", "Meanwhile", "the", "battle", "of", "the", "chasing", "pack", "continues", "with", "Manchester", "United", "securing", "what", "could", "prove", "to", "be", "a", "crucial", "three", "points", "in", "the", "race", "for", "Champions", "League", "football", "as", "they", "left", "it", "late", "to", "defeat", "Aston", "Villa", "Elsewhere", "in", "the", "table", "the", "competition", "for", "points", "is", "just", "as", "fierce", "with", "Sheffield", "United", "defeating", "Luton", "to", "keep", "a", "glimmer", "of", "hope", "alive", "that", "they", "can", "make", "the", "most", "unlikely", "of", "pushes", "for", "Premier", "League", "safety", "To", "gain", "a", "deeper", "insight", "into", "the", "emotions", "involved", "in", "top", "flight", "football", "Mail", "Sport", "have", "enlisted", "forensic", "lip", "reader", "Jeremy", "Freeman", "to", "offer", "his", "analysis", "on", "what", "was", "said", "in", "some", "of", "the", "weekend", "s", "most", "animated", "incidents", "After", "narrowly", "escaping", "relegation", "last", "season", "Nottingham", "Forest", "once", "again", "find", "themselves", "dicing", "with", "death", "at", "the", "wrong", "end", "of", "the", "table", "Steve", "Cooper", "s", "sacking", "in", "December", "was", "followed", "by", "back", "to", "back", "wins", "for", "Nuno", "Espirito", "Santo", "but", "that", "new", "manager", "bounce", "could", "yet", "be", "negated", "by", "a", "possible", "points", "penalty", "for", "breaking", "the", "league", "s", "financial", "rules", "The", "Tricky", "Trees", "are", "now", "slipping", "back", "into", "their", "old", "ways", "on", "the", "pitch", "and", "found", "themselves", "winless", "in", "three", "ahead", "of", "Newcastle", "s", "visit", "to", "the", "City", "Ground", "Bruno", "Guimaraes", "gave", "the", "visitors", "the", "perfect", "start", "but", "Forest", "fought", "back", "twice", "to", "head", "into", "the", "interval", "level", "In", "the", "second", "half", "Taiwo", "Awoniyi", "was", "brought", "down", "by", "Martin", "Dubravka", "with", "former", "referee", "Mark", "Clattenburg", "telling", "Mail", "Sport", "it", "was", "impossible", "for", "the", "striker", "to", "stay", "on", "his", "feet", "However", "referee", "Anthony", "Taylor", "did", "not", "point", "to", "spot", "leading", "to", "furious", "protests", "on", "the", "Forest", "bench", "captured", "on", "the", "broadcast", "that", "were", "only", "exacerbated", "after", "the", "referee", "cautioned", "Santo", "s", "assistant", "Rui", "Pedro", "Silva", "In", "his", "analysis", "of", "the", "clip", "Freeman", "noted", "the", "No", "2", "saying", "Hey", "Hey", "indecipherable", "That", "is", "nothing", "I", "was", "sitting", "on", "the", "bench", "I", "was", "sitting", "on", "the", "bench", "man", "of", "course", "sitting", "on", "the", "b", "y", "bench", "Things", "would", "go", "from", "bad", "to", "worse", "for", "the", "hosts", "in", "short", "order", "with", "Guimaraes", "again", "popping", "up", "to", "fire", "Newcastle", "to", "victory", "and", "secure", "the", "three", "points", "After", "victory", "over", "Liverpool", "kept", "their", "title", "ambitions", "alive", "Arsenal", "travelled", "to", "the", "London", "Stadium", "on", "Sunday", "intent", "on", "reaffirming", "their", "status", "as", "genuine", "contenders", "Mikel", "Arteta", "s", "side", "wasted", "little", "time", "getting", "down", "to", "business", "at", "the", "London", "Stadium", "With", "the", "game", "still", "level", "in", "the", "early", "stages", "Alphonse", "Areola", "attempted", "to", "kickstart", "a", "counter", "for", "the", "Hammers", "by", "launching", "a", "throw", "towards", "Edson", "Alvarez", "on", "the", "left", "flank", "The", "summer", "signing", "s", "first", "touch", "flattered", "to", "deceive", "however", "and", "he", "was", "forced", "into", "a", "rash", "challenge", "to", "deny", "an", "onrushing", "Bukayo", "Saka", "possession", "With", "the", "England", "international", "left", "writhing", "on", "the", "pitch", "Alvarez", "was", "shown", "a", "yellow", "card", "and", "according", "to", "Freeman", "was", "not", "expecting", "his", "caution", "No", "no", "nah", "no", "he", "didn", "t", "hurtâ", "referee", "then", "brandishes", "yellow", "â", "what", "Gabriel", "then", "involved", "himself", "by", "squaring", "up", "to", "Alvarez", "with", "the", "pair", "exchanging", "heated", "words", "F", "k", "off", "you", "dirty", "c", "t", "Freeman", "believes", "Gabriel", "to", "have", "told", "the", "West", "Ham", "defender", "with", "the", "second", "expletive", "matching", "the", "lip", "patterns", "and", "the", "context", "of", "the", "situation", "Alvarez", "retorts", "F", "k", "off", "Magalhaes", "Gabriel", "s", "surname", "how", "can", "you", "before", "the", "camera", "cuts", "away", "The", "Brazilian", "would", "ultimately", "have", "the", "last", "laugh", "joining", "Saka", "on", "the", "scoresheet", "in", "a", "6-0", "thumping", "as", "they", "handed", "the", "Hammers", "their", "joint", "heaviest", "home", "defeat", "in", "Premier", "League", "history", "For", "as", "jubilant", "an", "afternoon", "as", "Sunday", "was", "for", "the", "Gunners", "it", "was", "equally", "as", "devastating", "for", "David", "Moyes", "The", "Scotsman", "s", "second", "spell", "in", "charge", "at", "the", "east", "London", "club", "has", "been", "punctuated", "by", "moments", "of", "triumph", "followed", "by", "sinking", "despair", "and", "unfortunately", "for", "Moyes", "recent", "results", "have", "fallen", "squarely", "in", "the", "latter", "category", "Such", "was", "the", "disappointment", "of", "the", "defeat", "contract", "extension", "talks", "for", "the", "manager", "have", "been", "paused", "with", "the", "club", "now", "winless", "in", "their", "last", "seven", "games", "in", "all", "competitions", "Freeman", "s", "analysis", "of", "the", "former", "Everton", "boss", "s", "words", "captures", "the", "frustration", "of", "a", "manager", "watching", "his", "team", "completely", "blown", "out", "of", "the", "water", "In", "the", "84th", "minute", "the", "cameras", "cut", "to", "an", "exasperated", "Moyes", "who", "can", "be", "seen", "muttering", "to", "himself", "after", "Jakub", "Kiwior", "is", "penalised", "for", "a", "foul", "on", "Mohammed", "Kudus", "For", "f", "sake", "it", "s", "about", "time", "how", "many", "times", "it", "s", "not", "indecipherable", "count", "how", "many", "fouls", "While", "West", "Ham", "s", "momentum", "has", "ground", "to", "a", "halt", "in", "recent", "weeks", "Manchester", "United", "have", "very", "much", "been", "in", "the", "ascendency", "Erik", "ten", "Hag", "has", "spent", "much", "of", "the", "campaign", "to", "this", "point", "trying", "to", "reignite", "the", "success", "of", "his", "maiden", "term", "in", "Manchester", "and", "with", "a", "youthful", "spine", "at", "its", "core", "it", "looks", "to", "finally", "be", "underway", "Against", "Aston", "Villa", "United", "faced", "one", "of", "their", "primary", "rivals", "for", "a", "Champions", "League", "place", "and", "proved", "they", "can", "get", "a", "result", "at", "a", "critical", "juncture", "of", "the", "campaign", "Rasmus", "Hojlund", "continued", "his", "fine", "form", "in", "front", "of", "goal", "with", "a", "fifth", "in", "as", "many", "games", "before", "Douglas", "Luiz", "equalised", "for", "the", "hosts", "and", "likely", "ruffled", "a", "few", "feathers", "with", "an", "exuberant", "goal", "celebration", "How", "fitting", "then", "that", "the", "pair", "would", "come", "together", "in", "stoppage", "time", "after", "substitute", "Scott", "McTominay", "had", "fired", "United", "back", "into", "the", "lead", "with", "a", "header", "in", "the", "closing", "minutes", "of", "normal", "time", "As", "Hojlund", "walked", "off", "the", "pitch", "after", "being", "replaced", "by", "Jonny", "Evans", "the", "young", "forward", "enraged", "the", "Villa", "Park", "faithful", "by", "gesturing", "at", "them", "to", "calm", "down", "and", "reminding", "them", "of", "the", "score", "Luiz", "then", "confronted", "the", "Dane", "with", "Freeman", "noting", "he", "said", "You", "s", "come", "on", "you", "know", "you", "push", "off", "just", "go", "off", "as", "he", "attempted", "to", "hasten", "his", "departure", "A", "more", "fiery", "remark", "was", "still", "to", "come", "however", "with", "a", "fan", "wearing", "a", "club", "branded", "hoodie", "aiming", "a", "expletive", "laden", "diatribe", "at", "the", "21", "year", "old", "and", "appearing", "to", "refer", "to", "the", "him", "as", "a", "n", "e", "You", "f", "f", "off", "you", "f", "n", "e", "he", "could", "be", "seen", "shouting", "at", "the", "Dane"], "iob_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Jose", "Mourinho", "is", "being", "discussed", "at", "Bayern", "Munich", "The", "Portuguese", "has", "been", "in", "talks", "with", "Saudi", "Pro", "League", "clubs", "after", "being", "sacked", "by", "AS", "Roma", "However", "BILD", "says", "Bayern", "are", "now", "considering", "Mourinho", "as", "a", "replacement", "for", "Thomas", "Tuchel", "Former", "Chelsea", "boss", "Tuchel", "is", "under", "increasing", "pressure", "at", "Bayern", "as", "they", "lose", "ground", "in", "the", "Bundesliga", "title", "race", "Bayern", "were", "hammered", "3-0", "at", "home", "by", "Bayer", "Leverkusen", "on", "Saturday", "Mourinho", "remains", "in", "contact", "with", "the", "SPL", "but", "Bayern", "have", "now", "sparked", "his", "interest"], "iob_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PERF", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Champions", "League", "represents", "the", "only", "realistic", "chance", "of", "Barcelona", "winning", "a", "trophy", "this", "season", "given", "that", "they", "lost", "in", "the", "Spanish", "Super", "Cup", "final", "are", "out", "of", "the", "Copa", "del", "Rey", "and", "are", "10", "points", "adrift", "of", "Real", "Madrid", "in", "the", "La", "Liga", "title", "race", "Even", "then", "Xavi", "Hernandezâ", "s", "side", "will", "be", "considered", "as", "outsiders", "to", "win", "their", "sixth", "ever", "European", "cup", "given", "that", "they", "have", "been", "poor", "over", "the", "last", "few", "months", "Still", "they", "have", "as", "good", "a", "chance", "as", "any", "of", "winning", "the", "tournament", "although", "they", "have", "a", "very", "tough", "task", "to", "get", "past", "Napoli", "in", "their", "last", "16", "tie", "which", "kicks", "off", "next", "week", "with", "the", "first", "leg", "in", "Naples", "If", "Barcelona", "can", "pick", "up", "a", "positive", "result", "in", "that", "one", "they", "will", "have", "a", "good", "chance", "of", "reaching", "the", "quarter", "finals", "Barcelona", "have", "received", "some", "much", "needed", "good", "news", "ahead", "of", "that", "second", "leg", "at", "Montjuic", "as", "it", "has", "been", "reported", "by", "Relevo", "that", "La", "Liga", "have", "pencilled", "in", "their", "match", "with", "Mallorca", "for", "the", "8th", "of", "March", "which", "is", "a", "Friday", "It", "means", "that", "they", "will", "have", "an", "extra", "day", "of", "rest", "before", "the", "match", "against", "Napoli", "which", "takes", "place", "on", "the", "12th", "Itâ", "s", "uncommon", "for", "Barcelona", "to", "play", "in", "La", "Liga", "on", "a", "Friday", "itâ", "ll", "only", "be", "the", "second", "time", "this", "season", "that", "it", "has", "happened", "vs", "Sevilla", "on", "MD3", "Xavi", "and", "his", "players", "are", "sure", "to", "be", "grateful", "for", "the", "extra", "day", "to", "prepare", "which", "they", "will", "certainly", "need"], "iob_tags": ["O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Barcelona", "have", "expressed", "their", "condonlences", "following", "the", "passing", "of", "Joan", "Casals", "at", "the", "age", "of", "90", "commonly", "known", "as", "â", "the", "grandfather", "of", "Barcaâ", "Beginning", "with", "President", "Joan", "Laporta", "a", "number", "of", "figures", "came", "out", "to", "share", "their", "grief", "at", "his", "passing", "â", "Always", "by", "Barcaâ", "s", "side", "and", "active", "in", "â", "Barcelonaismâ", "from", "Guardiola", "de", "Bergueda", "his", "small", "and", "beloved", "homeland", "the", "Culers", "will", "never", "forget", "you", "Joan", "the", "Grandfather", "of", "Barca", "My", "condolences", "to", "family", "and", "friends", "â", "The", "likes", "of", "Marc", "Bartra", "Alexia", "Putellas", "and", "Ansu", "Fati", "all", "posted", "on", "social", "media", "about", "Casals", "folllowing", "the", "news", "Iconic", "for", "his", "beard", "and", "vintage", "Barcelona", "shirt", "the", "genesis", "of", "his", "fame", "comes", "from", "an", "old", "cartoon", "As", "highlighted", "by", "Esport3", "Valenti", "Castanys", "originally", "drew", "a", "figure", "that", "would", "come", "to", "resemble", "Casals", "later", "before", "a", "statue", "of", "â", "the", "grandfather", "of", "Barcaâ", "was", "erected", "outside", "of", "the", "original", "La", "Masia", "building", "Casals", "began", "going", "to", "games", "regularly", "in", "the", "eighties", "and", "quickly", "became", "a", "cult", "hero", "amongst", "Blaugrana", "fans"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-TEAM", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Montpellier", "will", "be", "hoping", "to", "get", "back", "on", "track", "following", "a", "hefty", "Coupe", "de", "France", "defeat", "at", "the", "hands", "of", "Nice", "midweek", "However", "they", "will", "face", "an", "in", "form", "Lyon", "side", "who", "have", "beaten", "Lille", "and", "Marseille", "in", "their", "last", "two", "outings", "Lâ", "Ã", "quipe", "report", "that", "Michel", "Der", "Zakarian", "is", "set", "to", "change", "things", "up", "against", "Lyon", "including", "a", "change", "of", "formation", "to", "a", "5", "2", "3", "instead", "of", "the", "4", "4", "2", "formation", "which", "he", "deployed", "against", "Nice", "This", "change", "in", "formation", "should", "see", "changes", "throughout", "the", "pitch", "The", "first", "of", "these", "changes", "coming", "in", "defence", "with", "ThÃ", "o", "Saint", "Luce", "dropping", "to", "the", "bench", "in", "favour", "of", "Lucas", "Mincarelli", "at", "left", "back", "With", "one", "additional", "defender", "Kouyate", "should", "also", "start", "with", "LÃ", "o", "Leroy", "the", "eventual", "casualty", "in", "midfield", "TÃ", "ji", "Savanier", "should", "drop", "back", "into", "midfield", "to", "form", "a", "double", "pivot", "Two", "changes", "are", "also", "expected", "in", "the", "attack", "with", "Akor", "Adams", "and", "Arnaud", "Nordin", "joining", "Yann", "Karamoh", "Benjamin", "Lecomte", "â", "Silvan", "Hefti", "BÃ", "cir", "OmeragiÄ", "Boubakar", "KouyatÃ", "Modibo", "Sangan", "Lucas", "Mincarelli", "â", "TÃ", "ji", "Savanier", "Joris", "Chotard", "â", "Arnaud", "Nordin", "Akor", "Adams", "Yann", "Karamoh"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Game", "is", "over", "and", "the", "final", "score", "is", "Milan", "1", "0", "Napoli", "Here", "is", "the", "match", "report", "0", "The", "match", "is", "about", "to", "start", "6", "Highlight", "from", "Milan", "vs", "Napoli", "9", "IbrahimoviÄ", "back", "to", "San", "Siro", "to", "watch", "the", "game", "11", "CLOSE", "Simeoneâ", "s", "shot", "wide", "out", "25", "Theo", "with", "the", "perfect", "finish", "Milan", "1", "0", "Napoli", "46", "Match", "Event", "for", "Milan", "vs", "Napoli", "49", "Cheek", "goes", "down", "in", "the", "box", "but", "ref", "says", "no", "penalty", "58", "Florenzi", "makes", "an", "important", "clearance", "60", "CLOSE", "Politanoâ", "s", "shot", "wide", "out", "61", "Theoâ", "s", "shot", "saved", "by", "Goalkeeper", "65", "Match", "Event", "for", "Milan", "vs", "Napoli", "68", "Match", "Event", "for", "Milan", "vs", "Napoli", "69", "Leao", "misses", "a", "golden", "chance", "Milan", "XI", "Kjaer", "Giroud", "Maignan", "Loftus", "Cheek", "Calabria", "Bennacer", "Theo", "Pulisic", "Gabbia", "Yacine", "Adli", "Leao", "Subs", "Mirante", "Florenzi", "Sportiello", "Jovic", "Noah", "Okafor", "Yunus", "Musah", "Filippo", "Terracciano", "Jan", "Carlo", "Simic", "Ã", "lex", "JimÃ", "nez", "Victor", "Eletu", "Napoli", "XI", "Juan", "Zielinski", "Di", "Lorenzo", "Lobotka", "Rrahmani", "Gollini", "G", "Simeone", "Pasquale", "Mazzocchi", "Anguissa", "Khvicha", "Kvaratskhelia", "Leo", "Ã", "stigÃ", "rd", "Subs", "Dendoncker", "Politano", "Nikita", "Contini", "M", "Olivera", "Jens", "Cajuste", "Giacomo", "Raspadori", "Cyril", "Ngonge", "Hamed", "Junior", "TraorÃ", "Jesper", "LindstrÃ", "m", "Natan"], "iob_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Jamie", "Carragher", "has", "had", "his", "say", "on", "who", "he", "believes", "will", "become", "the", "next", "Liverpool", "manager", "The", "Reds", "are", "on", "the", "market", "for", "a", "new", "manager", "after", "Jurgen", "Klopp", "announced", "last", "month", "that", "he", "will", "leave", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "season", "A", "number", "of", "fans", "in", "the", "Premier", "League", "and", "Europe", "have", "been", "linked", "with", "the", "vacancy", "but", "Carragher", "believes", "there", "is", "one", "standout", "candidate"], "iob_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Pep", "Guardiola", "was", "left", "to", "rue", "injuries", "to", "Jack", "Grealish", "and", "Bernardo", "Silva", "after", "Manchester", "City", "returned", "to", "Champions", "League", "action", "with", "a", "3", "1", "win", "at", "FC", "Copenhagen", "on", "Tuesday", "Grealish", "handed", "his", "first", "start", "in", "six", "matches", "lasted", "just", "21", "minutes", "of", "the", "holdersâ", "largely", "straightforward", "last", "16", "first", "leg", "success", "at", "Parken", "Stadium", "before", "being", "forced", "off", "with", "a", "groin", "injury", "Silva", "who", "put", "City", "into", "a", "2", "1", "lead", "just", "before", "the", "break", "with", "a", "fine", "flicked", "finish", "took", "a", "knock", "to", "the", "ankle", "late", "in", "the", "game", "Bernardo", "Silva", "centre", "takes", "on", "FC", "Copenhagenâ", "s", "Rasmus", "Falk", "right", "and", "Magnus", "Mattson", "The", "double", "blow", "comes", "after", "Josko", "Gvardiol", "missed", "the", "game", "with", "an", "ankle", "injury", "and", "Mateo", "Kovacic", "was", "also", "unavailable", "City", "manager", "Guardiola", "said", "â", "Itâ", "s", "something", "muscular", "with", "Jack", "his", "groin", "â", "He", "felt", "it", "on", "the", "grass", "started", "to", "complain", "The", "players", "can", "feel", "it", "immediately", "if", "itâ", "s", "muscular", "Itâ", "s", "a", "pity", "heâ", "s", "gutted", "â", "He", "wanted", "to", "continue", "but", "we", "didnâ", "t", "want", "to", "make", "the", "damage", "even", "worse", "Weâ", "ll", "make", "tests", "tomorrow", "â", "Bernardo", "has", "a", "big", "knock", "in", "his", "ankle", "and", "Josko", "is", "out", "two", "to", "three", "weeks", "Kova", "is", "ready", "to", "come", "back", "â", "The", "injuries", "took", "the", "gloss", "off", "what", "was", "a", "mainly", "comfortable", "night", "for", "City", "Kevin", "De", "Bruyne", "celebrates", "his", "opener", "against", "FC", "Copenhagen", "They", "took", "an", "early", "lead", "through", "Kevin", "De", "Bruyne", "and", "dominant", "in", "all", "departments", "should", "have", "led", "by", "more", "before", "Magnus", "Mattsson", "levelled", "after", "an", "Ederson", "error", "Silva", "restored", "the", "lead", "and", "Phil", "Foden", "gave", "the", "scoreline", "a", "more", "realistic", "look", "in", "stoppage", "time", "Guardiola", "said", "â", "It", "was", "really", "really", "good", "Iâ", "m", "so", "proud", "we", "played", "at", "that", "tempo", "It", "was", "perfect", "â", "We", "were", "patient", "in", "the", "right", "moments", "but", "itâ", "s", "not", "done", "I", "know", "how", "difficult", "it", "is", "â", "Itâ", "s", "not", "decisive", "but", "a", "good", "result", "Hopefully", "we", "can", "finish", "at", "home", "in", "front", "of", "our", "own", "people", "and", "go", "to", "the", "next", "round", "â", "Danish", "champions", "Copenhagen", "had", "not", "played", "competitively", "for", "two", "months", "due", "to", "their", "leagueâ", "s", "winter", "break", "and", "their", "rustiness", "was", "evident", "Advantage", "Man", "City", "UCL", "pic", "twitter", "com", "VDxLKzYUZ7", "â", "UEFA", "Champions", "League", "ChampionsLeague", "February", "13", "2024", "Coach", "Jacob", "Neestrup", "admitted", "it", "will", "now", "take", "something", "spectacular", "to", "progress", "but", "will", "not", "give", "up", "He", "said", "â", "Of", "course", "itâ", "s", "going", "to", "be", "difficult", "but", "now", "we", "have", "three", "games", "in", "the", "Danish", "league", "where", "we", "need", "to", "get", "results", "Then", "we", "take", "the", "away", "game", "where", "we", "try", "to", "do", "our", "very", "very", "best", "â", "The", "players", "did", "everything", "they", "could", "I", "canâ", "t", "blame", "them", "for", "anything", "We", "played", "against", "a", "top", "top", "team", "who", "know", "exactly", "what", "to", "do", "in", "every", "situation", "â", "I", "think", "City", "came", "with", "a", "very", "very", "professional", "mindset", "They", "took", "control", "of", "the", "game", "from", "the", "first", "second", "â"], "iob_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PERF", "B-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-COMP", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["We", "bring", "you", "the", "player", "ratings", "for", "Sevilla", "vs", "Atletico", "Madrid", "as", "Isaac", "Romero", "becomes", "Man", "of", "the", "Match", "with", "a", "rating", "of", "7", "8", "Any", "thoughts", "on", "the", "ratings", "Leave", "your", "opinion", "in", "the", "comments"], "iob_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Former", "AC", "Milan", "captain", "Massimo", "Ambrosini", "insists", "Mike", "Maignan", "will", "shake", "off", "his", "form", "slump", "Ambrosini", "is", "adamant", "Maignan", "remains", "the", "best", "goalkeeper", "in", "Serie", "A", "He", "told", "DAZN", "For", "me", "he", "remains", "the", "strongest", "goalkeeper", "in", "the", "championship", "even", "if", "he", "has", "had", "some", "setbacks", "Maybe", "what", "happened", "in", "Udine", "is", "in", "my", "head", "They", "tell", "me", "about", "it", "as", "a", "sensitive", "boy", "The", "emotional", "management", "of", "some", "situations", "may", "have", "been", "difficult", "On", "the", "Diavolo", "s", "positive", "return", "to", "form", "Ambrosini", "then", "added", "Whose", "credit", "is", "it", "for", "this", "Milan", "that", "has", "changed", "gear", "since", "December", "The", "answer", "is", "in", "the", "numbers", "in", "the", "last", "5", "matches", "Stefano", "Pioli", "s", "team", "has", "scored", "14", "goals", "They", "have", "not", "reached", "a", "defensive", "balance", "but", "he", "increased", "the", "threat", "and", "goal", "scoring", "rate", "this", "allowed", "him", "to", "stay", "in", "contact", "with", "those", "two", "up", "front"], "iob_tags": ["O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rio", "Ferdinand", "has", "named", "his", "preferred", "front", "six", "for", "England", "at", "Euro", "2024", "as", "the", "huge", "tournament", "edges", "closer", "this", "summer", "Three", "Lions", "boss", "Gareth", "Southgate", "will", "have", "some", "huge", "calls", "to", "make", "for", "his", "England", "squad", "as", "they", "prepare", "to", "jet", "off", "to", "Germany", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "current", "season", "looking", "for", "their", "first", "piece", "of", "silverware", "since", "1966", "There", "has", "been", "plenty", "of", "debate", "around", "the", "England", "line", "up", "and", "which", "players", "should", "get", "the", "nod", "to", "give", "the", "team", "the", "best", "chance", "of", "success", "and", "former", "England", "and", "Man", "United", "defender", "Ferdinand", "has", "come", "up", "with", "his", "best", "six", "players", "at", "the", "front", "end", "of", "the", "pitch", "Ferdinand", "who", "was", "working", "as", "a", "pundit", "for", "TNT", "s", "Champions", "League", "coverage", "of", "Man", "City", "s", "3", "1", "win", "against", "FC", "Copenhagen", "was", "asked", "for", "his", "thoughts", "on", "the", "best", "attacking", "line", "up", "after", "Phil", "Foden", "had", "netted", "City", "s", "third", "in", "stoppage", "time", "His", "first", "two", "picks", "at", "right", "wing", "and", "up", "front", "were", "simple", "and", "surprised", "no", "one", "Bukayo", "Saka", "right", "Harry", "Kane", "up", "front", "he", "began", "before", "his", "selections", "became", "trickier", "adding", "The", "left", "is", "tough", "man", "Jack", "Grealish", "is", "injured", "now", "Marcus", "Rashford", "hasnâ", "t", "been", "in", "form", "He", "was", "pushed", "for", "an", "answer", "by", "fellow", "former", "Three", "Lion", "Joleon", "Lescott", "who", "asked", "him", "to", "give", "a", "verdict", "if", "everyone", "was", "fit", "Ferdinand", "replied", "If", "everyoneâ", "s", "fit", "and", "flying", "Rashford", "plays", "for", "me", "on", "the", "left", "Lescott", "agreed", "with", "his", "front", "three", "selection", "adding", "Yeah", "Iâ", "d", "go", "for", "that", "I", "donâ", "t", "think", "thereâ", "s", "a", "bad", "choice", "I", "think", "everyone", "thinks", "you", "can", "get", "it", "wrong", "and", "say", "well", "if", "youâ", "re", "picking", "him", "then", "you", "donâ", "t", "rate", "the", "other", "one", "I", "donâ", "t", "think", "thatâ", "s", "the", "case", "I", "think", "thereâ", "s", "so", "much", "talent", "Ferdinand", "was", "then", "asked", "who", "he", "would", "have", "in", "the", "No", "10", "role", "should", "England", "play", "a", "4", "2", "3", "1", "formation", "Iâ", "d", "have", "Foden", "in", "there", "he", "said", "off", "the", "back", "his", "impressive", "display", "for", "City", "He", "also", "concurred", "with", "Lescott", "on", "a", "central", "midfield", "pairing", "of", "Jude", "Bellingham", "and", "Declan", "Rice", "behind", "Foden", "with", "the", "ex", "Everton", "man", "saying", "the", "trio", "would", "figure", "it", "out", "between", "them", "Ferdinand", "then", "pleaded", "with", "Southgate", "to", "ensure", "that", "he", "picked", "the", "same", "front", "six", "when", "he", "is", "asked", "to", "name", "his", "final", "squad", "later", "this", "summer", "If", "Gareth", "needs", "any", "help", "deciding", "that", "Iâ", "m", "here", "Iâ", "ll", "go", "on", "a", "Zoom", "call", "Iâ", "ll", "even", "come", "around", "your", "house", "and", "thatâ", "s", "your", "front", "six", "please", "England", "s", "preparations", "will", "continue", "with", "friendlies", "against", "Brazil", "and", "Belgium", "next", "month", "before", "two", "warm", "up", "games", "ahead", "of", "the", "Euros", "against", "Boznia", "and", "Iceland", "They", "ll", "kick", "off", "their", "Euro", "campaign", "against", "Serbia", "on", "June", "16", "before", "rounding", "off", "the", "group", "against", "Denmark", "and", "Slovenia"], "iob_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM"]}
{"tokens": ["Manchester", "United", "legend", "Gary", "Neville", "has", "dubbed", "the", "current", "crop", "of", "Red", "Devils", "an", "odd", "bunch", "after", "Sunday", "night", "s", "dramatic", "2", "1", "win", "away", "at", "Aston", "Villa", "Rasmus", "Hojlund", "fired", "Erik", "ten", "Hag", "s", "side", "in", "front", "early", "on", "to", "net", "his", "fifth", "league", "goal", "of", "the", "season", "but", "Douglas", "Luiz", "levelled", "things", "up", "midway", "through", "the", "second", "half", "There", "was", "still", "time", "for", "United", "to", "respond", "and", "in", "the", "85th", "minute", "Scott", "McTominay", "s", "bullet", "header", "left", "Villa", "goalkeeper", "Emi", "Martinez", "with", "no", "chance", "Though", "the", "win", "means", "United", "have", "taken", "a", "step", "closer", "to", "the", "Champions", "League", "qualification", "places", "Neville", "has", "made", "clear", "he", "wants", "to", "see", "more", "from", "his", "former", "side", "specifically", "the", "attacking", "trio", "of", "Hojlund", "Marcus", "Rashford", "and", "Alejandro", "Garnacho", "The", "front", "three", "look", "more", "settled", "â", "Hojlund", "Rashford", "and", "Garnacho", "Neville", "told", "Sky", "Sports", "follwing", "the", "late", "win", "at", "Villa", "Theyâ", "re", "better", "than", "they", "were", "but", "theyâ", "re", "still", "not", "great", "You", "still", "donâ", "t", "see", "any", "patterns", "or", "combinations", "They", "concede", "so", "many", "chances", "They", "donâ", "t", "control", "games", "They", "donâ", "t", "keep", "possession", "better", "than", "other", "teams", "But", "the", "do", "have", "players", "who", "can", "win", "matches", "Theyâ", "re", "a", "bit", "of", "an", "odd", "bunch", "They", "just", "play", "in", "moments", "during", "matches", "With", "that", "being", "said", "Neville", "did", "make", "clear", "that", "United", "are", "starting", "to", "turn", "the", "tide", "on", "their", "season", "and", "as", "a", "result", "the", "hopes", "of", "Champions", "League", "returning", "to", "Old", "Trafford", "next", "term", "are", "still", "alive", "He", "added", "We", "are", "now", "at", "the", "business", "end", "of", "the", "season", "Itâ", "s", "been", "so", "up", "and", "down", "for", "United", "We", "are", "at", "the", "stage", "where", "they", "are", "six", "pointers", "They", "couldâ", "ve", "been", "out", "of", "it", "but", "as", "they", "go", "over", "to", "those", "United", "fans", "they", "go", "within", "five", "points", "and", "touching", "distance", "of", "being", "able", "to", "catch", "them", "Villa", "Ten", "Hag", "s", "side", "now", "have", "until", "next", "Sunday", "to", "recover", "before", "they", "are", "in", "action", "again", "with", "the", "Red", "Devils", "s", "next", "outing", "coming", "in", "the", "form", "of", "another", "tricky", "away", "trip", "This", "time", "United", "meet", "Luton", "Town", "at", "Kenilworth", "Road", "United", "go", "into", "that", "meeting", "with", "Luton", "off", "the", "back", "of", "three", "successive", "league", "wins", "and", "momentum", "is", "starting", "to", "gather", "The", "expectant", "Old", "Trafford", "faithful", "are", "hoping", "that", "this", "time", "around", "their", "side", "can", "hit", "form", "at", "the", "right", "stage", "of", "the", "season", "and", "return", "to", "the", "Champions", "League"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-COMP", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP"]}
{"tokens": ["Orlando", "City", "signing", "Luis", "Muriel", "has", "posted", "an", "open", "farewell", "letter", "to", "Atalanta", "La", "Dea", "sold", "Muriel", "to", "Orlando", "for", "â", "1m", "The", "Colombian", "has", "now", "written", "an", "open", "letter", "to", "Atalanta", "Dear", "Atalanta", "fans", "I", "couldn", "t", "help", "but", "say", "hello", "and", "thank", "you", "before", "starting", "my", "new", "adventure", "in", "America", "I", "would", "have", "liked", "to", "do", "it", "in", "person", "but", "there", "wasn", "t", "time", "to", "plan", "a", "goodbye", "because", "as", "soon", "as", "the", "OK", "arrived", "I", "had", "to", "leave", "to", "do", "the", "medical", "visits", "with", "my", "new", "club", "before", "signing", "We", "ll", "find", "a", "way", "to", "see", "each", "other", "before", "long", "when", "I", "return", "to", "Italy", "Both", "I", "and", "the", "club", "want", "it", "However", "I", "really", "wanted", "to", "thank", "you", "now", "for", "the", "foour", "and", "a", "half", "wonderful", "years", "that", "I", "lived", "in", "Bergamo", "also", "thanks", "to", "you", "You", "have", "always", "supported", "me", "and", "conveyed", "great", "affection", "and", "warmth", "I", "felt", "loved", "as", "a", "footballer", "but", "also", "as", "a", "person", "I", "will", "never", "forget", "you", "Then", "in", "another", "passage", "he", "added", "Together", "we", "experienced", "beautiful", "unforgettable", "emotions", "and", "did", "great", "things", "in", "Europe", "and", "Italy", "together", "with", "the", "Percassi", "family", "Mister", "Gasperini", "and", "all", "my", "splendid", "companions", "Bergamo", "will", "always", "remain", "in", "my", "heart", "like", "a", "second", "home", "Thank", "you", "for", "all", "the", "messages", "of", "affection", "these", "days", "I", "hope", "you", "will", "follow", "me", "with", "sympathy", "also", "in", "my", "new", "adventure", "in", "Orlando", "I", "will", "always", "take", "you", "with", "me", "Thank", "you", "very", "much", "I", "hug", "you", "all", "See", "you", "soon", "and", "go", "Atalanta"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM"]}
{"tokens": ["Arsenal", "have", "kept", "their", "title", "challenge", "well", "on", "track", "with", "a", "statement", "6", "0", "victory", "away", "to", "West", "Ham", "Mikel", "Artetaâ", "s", "Gunners", "ran", "rampant", "at", "the", "London", "Stadium", "to", "keep", "the", "pace", "with", "Liverpool", "and", "Manchester", "City", "Itâ", "s", "the", "Gunnersâ", "biggest", "ever", "away", "win", "in", "the", "Premier", "League", "but", "where", "does", "it", "rank", "overall", "Weâ", "ve", "taken", "a", "closer", "look", "at", "Arsenalâ", "s", "five", "biggest", "Premier", "League", "wins", "Sat", "in", "his", "dugout", "at", "the", "London", "Stadium", "David", "Moyes", "must", "have", "had", "horrible", "flashbacks", "to", "the", "time", "his", "Everton", "side", "got", "demolished", "by", "Arsenal", "almost", "two", "decades", "ago", "The", "game", "is", "most", "memorable", "for", "Dennis", "Bergkamp", "putting", "in", "a", "late", "career", "masterclass", "notching", "three", "assists", "and", "a", "goal", "in", "a", "man", "of", "the", "match", "display", "in", "the", "Gunnersâ", "final", "home", "match", "of", "the", "2004", "05", "campaign", "The", "legendary", "Dutchmanâ", "s", "contract", "was", "up", "that", "summer", "but", "he", "was", "persuaded", "to", "sign", "for", "one", "more", "year", "â", "Arsenalâ", "s", "last", "season", "at", "Highbury", "â", "after", "being", "serenaded", "with", "chants", "of", "â", "one", "more", "yearâ", "from", "the", "Arsenal", "faithful", "that", "day", "Arguably", "Arsenalâ", "s", "finest", "hour", "in", "that", "legendarily", "sexy", "burgundy", "o2", "sponsored", "kit", "of", "2005", "06", "Thierry", "Henry", "was", "on", "fire", "with", "a", "hat", "trick", "that", "took", "him", "to", "150", "Premier", "League", "goals", "â", "level", "with", "Cliff", "Bastinâ", "s", "league", "record", "for", "the", "club", "Wenger", "was", "delighted", "with", "his", "sideâ", "s", "display", "against", "Steve", "McClarenâ", "s", "sorry", "Smoggies", "and", "was", "keen", "to", "dish", "the", "credit", "around", "â", "We", "played", "our", "game", "and", "the", "goals", "came", "as", "a", "consequence", "of", "the", "quality", "of", "our", "game", "â", "the", "Frenchman", "told", "the", "BBC", "â", "Of", "course", "Thierry", "scored", "three", "â", "and", "everybody", "nearly", "scored", "But", "Reyes", "contributed", "with", "his", "final", "balls", "and", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "is", "that", "the", "team", "plays", "the", "game", "we", "want", "to", "play", "and", "plays", "with", "a", "great", "spirit", "â", "In", "their", "next", "home", "game", "Wengerâ", "s", "Gunners", "lost", "3", "2", "to", "West", "Ham", "â", "which", "proved", "to", "be", "the", "last", "ever", "defeat", "they", "suffered", "at", "Highbury", "The", "2011", "12", "season", "was", "also", "notable", "for", "Arsenalâ", "s", "record", "Premier", "League", "defeat", "â", "the", "infamous", "8", "2", "away", "to", "Manchester", "United", "in", "the", "early", "weeks", "of", "the", "campaign", "But", "come", "late", "winter", "Arsenal", "had", "turned", "their", "form", "around", "and", "put", "their", "injury", "woes", "behind", "them", "Deadline", "day", "additions", "Mikel", "Arteta", "and", "Per", "Mertesacker", "made", "a", "major", "impact", "and", "were", "really", "clicking", "by", "the", "time", "Blackburn", "came", "to", "the", "Emirates", "in", "February", "Gael", "Givet", "was", "sent", "off", "for", "Steve", "Keanâ", "s", "relegation", "bound", "Blackburn", "Robin", "van", "Persie", "scored", "a", "hat", "trick", "Alex", "Oxlade", "Chamberlain", "notched", "a", "brace", "and", "Arteta", "also", "got", "himself", "on", "the", "scoresheet", "A", "great", "Morten", "Gamst", "Pedersen", "free", "kick", "proved", "scant", "consolation", "for", "Blackburn", "whose", "misery", "was", "compounded", "with", "a", "Scott", "Dann", "own", "goal", "injury", "time", "Itâ", "s", "easy", "to", "forget", "now", "that", "Arsenal", "came", "in", "2024", "in", "a", "despondent", "mood", "Back", "to", "back", "defeats", "to", "West", "Ham", "and", "Fulham", "at", "the", "back", "end", "of", "the", "year", "left", "their", "title", "hopes", "on", "the", "ropes", "and", "they", "went", "to", "be", "eliminated", "from", "the", "FA", "Cup", "at", "home", "to", "Liverpool", "But", "Artetaâ", "s", "men", "have", "bounced", "back", "in", "emphatic", "fashion", "with", "a", "100", "winning", "record", "in", "the", "Premier", "League", "including", "a", "statement", "victory", "over", "Liverpool", "Their", "reinvigorated", "confident", "mood", "was", "typified", "by", "their", "brutal", "and", "ruthless", "display", "away", "to", "the", "Hammers", "avenging", "their", "two", "earlier", "defeats", "to", "Moyesâ", "Hammers", "by", "hitting", "them", "for", "six", "Arsenalâ", "s", "one", "other", "six", "nil", "win", "of", "the", "Premier", "League", "came", "against", "Ian", "H0llowayâ", "s", "newly", "promoted", "Blackpool", "in", "the", "early", "weeks", "of", "the", "2010", "11", "season", "The", "Tangerines", "made", "a", "great", "fist", "of", "survival", "and", "weâ", "re", "seemingly", "obliged", "to", "describe", "them", "as", "a", "breath", "of", "fresh", "air", "but", "they", "were", "still", "very", "much", "finding", "their", "feet", "at", "that", "point", "Theo", "Walcott", "scored", "a", "hat", "trick", "while", "Andrey", "Arshavin", "Abou", "Diaby", "and", "even", "Marouane", "Chamakh", "got", "themselves", "on", "the", "scoresheet"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERF", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF"]}
{"tokens": ["Barcelona", "are", "unlikely", "to", "have", "much", "money", "to", "spend", "in", "the", "summer", "and", "so", "the", "pressure", "will", "be", "on", "Deco", "to", "get", "it", "right", "with", "the", "players", "he", "can", "bring", "in", "His", "view", "is", "that", "the", "Blaugrana", "need", "to", "bring", "in", "more", "physically", "gifted", "players", "According", "to", "Sport", "Barcelona", "will", "look", "to", "get", "stronger", "and", "faster", "in", "the", "transfer", "market", "this", "summer", "with", "Deco", "feeling", "they", "lack", "sufficient", "power", "to", "compete", "with", "their", "rivals", "That", "is", "part", "of", "the", "thinking", "behind", "their", "interest", "in", "Everton", "midfielder", "Amadou", "Onana", "who", "would", "give", "Barcelona", "that", "physical", "prowess", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "the", "park", "that", "they", "currently", "lack", "â", "You", "canâ", "t", "take", "a", "group", "of", "kids", "dress", "them", "in", "the", "Barca", "shirt", "and", "expect", "them", "to", "win", "titles", "from", "one", "day", "to", "the", "next", "â", "Deco", "said", "in", "a", "recent", "interview", "with", "Nascer", "do", "Sol", "â", "The", "team", "did", "not", "show", "in", "many", "games", "a", "physical", "and", "athletic", "capacity", "with", "which", "it", "could", "overcome", "its", "opponents", "â", "The", "problem", "for", "Deco", "is", "that", "it", "cuts", "to", "the", "heart", "of", "a", "heated", "style", "debate", "at", "Barcelona", "and", "by", "making", "out", "as", "if", "he", "wants", "to", "sacrifice", "technical", "quality", "for", "physical", "attributes", "he", "is", "likely", "to", "receive", "plenty", "of", "stick", "from", "fans", "Even", "if", "that", "is", "his", "intention", "he", "would", "be", "better", "off", "phrasing", "it", "differently", "or", "just", "not", "saying", "it", "all", "After", "his", "recent", "comments", "about", "â", "breaking", "from", "the", "pastâ", "went", "viral", "Deco", "is", "having", "to", "learn", "quickly", "that", "saying", "the", "wrong", "thing", "will", "create", "problems", "for", "him"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Napoli", "coach", "Walter", "Mazzarri", "insists", "their", "top", "four", "hopes", "aren", "t", "out", "of", "reach", "after", "defeat", "to", "AC", "Milan", "Milan", "won", "1", "0", "thanks", "to", "Theo", "Hernandez", "s", "winner", "Milan", "had", "a", "ferocious", "pressing", "in", "the", "first", "half", "and", "fell", "back", "after", "the", "break", "We", "did", "well", "but", "could", "ve", "done", "better", "to", "make", "the", "most", "of", "their", "dip", "in", "fitness", "levels", "Mazzarri", "told", "DAZN", "â", "I", "don", "t", "think", "the", "change", "of", "system", "was", "the", "key", "to", "playing", "better", "in", "the", "second", "half", "we", "simply", "did", "better", "â", "We", "had", "worked", "all", "week", "on", "the", "movements", "to", "deal", "with", "Theo", "doing", "that", "give", "and", "go", "I", "don", "t", "like", "specifying", "who", "made", "the", "mistake", "but", "we", "had", "prepared", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "and", "a", "mistake", "was", "made", "It", "was", "a", "predictable", "move", "because", "that", "is", "a", "classic", "Milan", "move", "so", "we", "should", "ve", "closed", "off", "the", "through", "ball", "earlier", "That", "is", "all", "I", "will", "say", "Napoli", "are", "seven", "points", "off", "fourth", "place", "Mazzarri", "added", "â", "The", "objective", "is", "to", "win", "as", "many", "games", "as", "we", "can", "It", "is", "possible", "We", "had", "many", "injuries", "missed", "important", "players", "we", "had", "a", "great", "performance", "tonight", "and", "did", "not", "deserve", "to", "lose", "â", "We", "proved", "again", "tonight", "that", "we", "played", "well", "and", "could", "ve", "taken", "three", "points", "if", "things", "had", "gone", "our", "way", "against", "one", "of", "the", "best", "teams", "in", "the", "league", "â", "Many", "of", "those", "ahead", "of", "us", "have", "to", "come", "to", "Naples", "so", "I", "have", "confidence", "we", "will", "challenge", "for", "at", "least", "fourth", "place"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-TEAM", "B-PERF", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PERF", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Chelsea", "are", "sweating", "on", "Thiago", "Silva", "s", "fitness", "ahead", "of", "the", "Carabao", "Cup", "final", "after", "the", "Brazilian", "defender", "limped", "out", "of", "Monday", "night", "s", "3", "1", "win", "at", "Crystal", "Palace", "The", "39", "year", "old", "injured", "his", "groin", "sliding", "in", "to", "block", "a", "shot", "by", "Palace", "s", "Jean", "Philippe", "Mateta", "around", "the", "hour", "mark", "and", "could", "be", "seen", "shaking", "his", "head", "when", "going", "off", "Chelsea", "manager", "Mauricio", "Pochettino", "later", "confirmed", "Silva", "felt", "something", "in", "his", "groin", "and", "would", "be", "assessed", "on", "Tuesday", "Any", "potential", "problem", "would", "add", "to", "a", "growing", "injury", "list", "for", "the", "Blues", "ahead", "of", "their", "trip", "to", "Manchester", "City", "in", "the", "Premier", "League", "on", "Saturday", "and", "the", "Carabao", "final", "with", "Liverpool", "at", "Wembley", "on", "February", "25", "They", "are", "already", "without", "defensive", "options", "as", "Benoit", "Badiashile", "faces", "a", "spell", "on", "the", "sidelines", "after", "suffering", "a", "groin", "injury", "of", "his", "own", "in", "the", "3", "1", "FA", "Cup", "win", "at", "Aston", "Villa", "Wesley", "Fofana", "hasn", "t", "featured", "at", "all", "this", "season", "after", "injuring", "his", "anterior", "cruciate", "ligament", "in", "his", "knee", "during", "pre", "season", "Reece", "James", "and", "Marc", "Cucurella", "are", "also", "out", "at", "the", "moment", "but", "should", "return", "at", "some", "point", "next", "month", "Chelsea", "came", "from", "a", "goal", "down", "to", "win", "at", "Selhurst", "Park", "thanks", "to", "a", "double", "from", "Conor", "Gallagher", "and", "another", "from", "Enzo", "Fernandez"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-COMP", "I-COMP", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"tokens": ["Manchester", "United", "and", "Ajax", "are", "scouting", "Casa", "Pia", "striker", "Leo", "Fajarda", "A", "Bola", "says", "the", "17", "year", "old", "is", "being", "watched", "by", "both", "clubs", "this", "season", "In", "recent", "weeks", "Ajax", "scouts", "have", "been", "spectators", "at", "Casa", "Pia", "games", "where", "the", "match", "against", "Benfica", "last", "week", "1", "1", "particularly", "attracted", "attention", "However", "the", "Amsterdammers", "were", "in", "good", "company", "Scouts", "from", "Paris", "Saint", "Germain", "AC", "Milan", "Manchester", "United", "and", "of", "course", "Sporting", "Portugal", "and", "Benfica", "were", "also", "present", "to", "see", "the", "talent", "at", "work", "Fajarda", "is", "not", "contractually", "bound", "to", "Casa", "Pia", "and", "will", "most", "likely", "have", "clubs", "to", "choose", "from", "next", "summer", "At", "the", "beginning", "of", "this", "season", "the", "17", "year", "old", "attacker", "left", "FC", "Porto", "s", "youth", "academy", "at", "his", "own", "request", "to", "move", "back", "to", "Lisbon"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Bayern", "Munich", "manager", "Thomas", "Tuchel", "has", "reportedly", "registered", "interest", "in", "replacing", "Xavi", "at", "Barcelona", "this", "summer", "Xavi", "revealed", "last", "month", "that", "he", "will", "be", "stepping", "down", "from", "his", "position", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "season", "leaving", "the", "Catalan", "giants", "looking", "for", "his", "successor", "And", "former", "Chelsea", "boss", "Tuchel", "has", "offered", "himself", "to", "Barcelona", "to", "take", "over", "in", "the", "dugout", "ahead", "of", "next", "season", "according", "to", "Mundo", "Deportivo", "Tuchel", "spoke", "glowingly", "about", "LaLiga", "in", "a", "recent", "interview", "as", "he", "talked", "up", "the", "prospect", "of", "coaching", "in", "Spain", "one", "day", "Moving", "abroad", "would", "appeal", "to", "me", "again", "he", "admitted", "Spain", "has", "an", "extraordinary", "league", "From", "my", "perspective", "and", "based", "on", "my", "experience", "working", "with", "Spaniards", "they", "are", "characterised", "by", "a", "tremendous", "amount", "of", "self", "confidence", "When", "you", "speak", "with", "Spanish", "players", "you", "quickly", "get", "the", "sense", "that", "you", "are", "engaging", "with", "the", "person", "This", "led", "to", "speculation", "linking", "him", "with", "the", "Barcelona", "job", "but", "Bayern", "quickly", "moved", "to", "quash", "these", "rumours"], "iob_tags": ["B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-MISC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-COMP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "agent", "of", "Nicola", "Zalewski", "has", "welcomed", "Daniele", "de", "Rossi", "s", "changes", "at", "AS", "Roma", "Giovanni", "Ferro", "is", "happy", "De", "Rossi", "replaced", "the", "sacked", "Jose", "Mourinho", "â", "Zalewski", "never", "wanted", "to", "leave", "in", "January", "that", "was", "not", "true", "as", "he", "has", "always", "supported", "Roma", "Ferro", "told", "Numero", "Diez", "â", "De", "Rossi", "returned", "him", "to", "his", "natural", "position", "the", "one", "he", "was", "accustomed", "to", "since", "he", "was", "a", "kid", "and", "now", "we", "expect", "him", "to", "make", "a", "step", "up", "in", "quality", "â", "If", "he", "is", "placed", "closer", "to", "the", "opposition", "goal", "it", "can", "only", "benefit", "him", "He", "is", "fresh", "quick", "sparkling", "so", "the", "fewer", "defensive", "obligations", "he", "has", "the", "more", "he", "can", "express", "his", "qualities"], "iob_tags": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "I-TEAM", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jose", "Mourinho", "hilariously", "explained", "he", "has", "had", "to", "tell", "former", "Chelsea", "star", "Michael", "Essien", "to", "stop", "calling", "him", "a", "certain", "name", "as", "he", "joked", "they", "are", "nearly", "the", "same", "age", "The", "61", "year", "old", "made", "the", "hilarious", "revelation", "when", "he", "was", "describing", "the", "loyalty", "that", "he", "has", "been", "shown", "by", "African", "players", "during", "his", "stellar", "managerial", "career", "Mourinho", "coached", "the", "likes", "of", "Didier", "Drogba", "Michael", "Essien", "and", "John", "Obi", "Mikel", "during", "his", "two", "stints", "at", "Stamford", "Bridge", "while", "also", "working", "with", "other", "players", "from", "the", "African", "continent", "elsewhere", "around", "Europe", "as", "well", "Having", "been", "sacked", "as", "Roma", "head", "coach", "in", "January", "following", "a", "difficult", "run", "of", "form", "Mourinho", "is", "now", "waiting", "for", "the", "next", "offer", "that", "convinces", "him", "to", "get", "back", "into", "top", "level", "football", "Delivering", "success", "at", "every", "club", "he", "has", "been", "at", "with", "the", "exception", "of", "Tottenham", "Mourinho", "has", "worked", "with", "some", "of", "the", "world", "s", "best", "players", "boasting", "a", "cv", "of", "training", "Cristiano", "Ronaldo", "Zlatan", "Ibrahimovic", "Wayne", "Rooney", "and", "others"], "iob_tags": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "B-TEAM", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "I-PERF", "I-PERF", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERF", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TEAM", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
